[00:10]Presenting
[00:17]ColdPlay
[00:24]Yellow
[00:33]Look at the stars
[00:36]Look how they shine for you
[00:41]And everything you do
[00:47]Yeah, they were all yellow
[00:50]I came along
[00:53]I wrote a song for you
[00:58]And all the things you do
[01:04]And it was called Yellow
[01:09]So then I took my turn
[01:15]Oh, what a thing to have done?
[01:20]And it was all yellow
[01:29]Your skin
[01:31]Oh yeah, your skin and bones
[01:34]Turn into something beautiful
[01:40]You know
[01:42]You know I love you so
[02:13]I swam across
[02:16]I jumped across for you
[02:21]Oh, what a thing to do?
[02:27]'Cause you were all yellow
[02:29]I drew a line
[02:32]I drew a line for you
[02:38]Oh, what a thing to do?
[02:43]And it was all yellow
[02:52]Your skin
[02:54]Oh yeah, your skin and bones
[02:57]Turn into something beautiful
[03:03]And you know
[03:05]For you I'd bleed myself dry
[03:35]It's true
[03:38]Look how they shine for you
[03:49]Look how they shine for
[03:55]Look how they shine for you
[04:06]Look how they shine
[04:09]Look at the stars
[04:12]Look how they shine for you
[04:17]And all the things that you do
